northpointe.com 2010-03-02

# Northpointe Bank - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to you, and we are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. We want you to understand what information we collect and how we use it.  Click on any of the links below to learn more about our Privacy Policy, and feel free to contact us with any additional questions.

**What Information We Collect**  
We may collect "nonpublic personal information" about you from the following sources: Information we receive from you on applications or other forms;  
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, and  
Information we receive from third parties such as consumer reporting agencies.  
"Nonpublic personal information" is nonpublic information about you that we obtain in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. For example, nonpublic personal information includes information regarding your account balance, payment history, and overdraft history. 

**What Information We Disclose**

We are permitted by law to disclose nonpublic personal information about you to third parties in certain circumstances. For example, we may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to third parties to assist us in servicing your loan or account with us, to government entities in response to subpoenas, and to consumer reporting agencies. We may also disclose the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform services on our behalf (for example, check printing companies) or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about you to any other third parties, except as permitted or required by law. Since this is our policy, there is nothing you need to do to request us not to share your nonpublic personal information with such third parties. 

If you decide to close your account(s) or become an inactive customer, we will continue to adhere to the privacy policies and practices described in this notice. 

**Our Security Procedures**

We also take steps to safeguard customer information. We restrict access to your personal and account information to those employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information. 

**Collection of Information From This Website**

Visitors to this website remain anonymous, unless they register for a service or otherwise elect to disclose their identity to us. Although we do not collect personally identifying information about persons who simply visit our site, we may use standard software to collect non-identifying information, such as: 

The date and time our site was accessed. The visitor's IP address (This numeric address is assigned automatically to a computer when it accesses the Internet. It is not linked to any personally identifiable information.) Web browser used City, state, and country.

We may place "cookies" on a computer to track a visitor's use of our website. A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on your hard drive. It takes up very little room on your system and helps us to customize our site and make its navigation easier for you. We sometimes use cookies to help estimate the number of visitors to our site and to determine which areas are the most popular. Unless you register with us for a service (such as online banking), the cookie does not provide us with any personally identifying information about you, such as your name or address.
